<?xml version='1.1' ?> 
<Aliases>
  <Alias>
		<Name>periodic</Name>
		<ReplaceBeforeArgs>python windows\periodic.py -args "</ReplaceBeforeArgs>
		<ReplaceAfterArgs>" -project Ops</ReplaceAfterArgs>
		<Help>
Usage: periodic [-h] [-f] [-i] [-n] [-p period] [ command to run ]
--period is the time between each command run.
  Time ranges (e.g. 5-25) will be randomized. Decimals are allowed.
  You can specify the period as: 5, 5-10, 5-10m, 30s, 30-60s, 4h, 1-2h, etc.
--foreground is useful for allowing you to see the output in your terminal
--ignore-errors to not stop on an error from the child command, 
  i.e. when a ping fails
--count is the maximum number of times periodic should run your command
--max-runtime is the maximum amount of time the periodic script will run 
By default, periodic waits for each command to finish before starting the 
  sleep timer. Use --no-wait for long running commands when you want to ensure 
  they spawn at the specified period, no matter how long each command takes. 
  Be careful when using this, you could really bog down the host or DSZ! 
If your command string requires double-quotes, use single-quotes instead and I'll replace them:
  e.g. periodic -p 1 log dir 'C:\Documents and Settings\joe\Desktop\*'
   [-p, --period period] (Optional, default 10-15 minutes)
	  The period at which to run the command
   [-f, --foreground] (Optional, default False)
      Don't background the main periodic command, keep output on the screen
   [-i, --ignore-errors] (Optional, default False)
      Don't stop on an error from the child command
   [-n, --no-wait] (Optional, default False)
      Don't wait for the command to finish, run each command asynchronously
   [-c, --count] (Optional, default None)
      Max number of times the command should run
   [-t, --max-runtime] (Optional, default None)
      Max runtime of the periodic command
   [command string] (Optional)
	  The DANDERSPRITZ command to run periodically
If no arguments are supplied, the operator is prompted for the command to run at the default period. 
Run with a -h for some example commands.
</Help>
<Options>
    <Option>h</Option>
    <Option>-help</Option>
    <Option>p</Option>
    <Option>-period</Option>
    <Option>n</Option>
    <Option>-no-wait</Option>
    <Option>f</Option>
    <Option>-foreground</Option>
    <Option>i</Option>
    <Option>-ignore-errors</Option>
    <Option>c</Option>
    <Option>-count</Option>
    <Option>t</Option>
    <Option>-max-runtime</Option>
</Options>
  </Alias>
</Aliases>